Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1963-1990; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  - 92nd Congress (), 1971-72
    - Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored
      - H.R. 13516, Reenfranchlsement Act of, 1972. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10315, H.R. 10318, Refuse Act Amendments. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 411, Reorganization Plan no.1. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 12166, Residential Real Property Taxes. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 7919, Retirement Income Exemption. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 7865, Salton Sea Project Study. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10398, School Construction Act. (Box 78)
      - H.Con.Res. 550, Security and Protection of Capitol. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 121, Select Committee on Aging. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11911, Service Contract Act Amendments. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10935, H.R. 10870, Sickle Cell Anemia Appropriations (2). (Box 78)
      - H.R. 8597, Sickle Cell Anemia Institute. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11170, Sick1e Ce11 Anemia Programs for District of Columbia. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11171, H~R. 11420, Sickle Cell Anemia Prevention Act. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16030, Social Security Household Maintaining Benefits. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16031, Social Security Insurance Benefits Amended. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16820, Public Assistance for Social Security Benefits for Increase., 1972 (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16032, Social Security Earnings to $9,000, Amended. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16033, Social Security Act to Eliminate Family Maximum Amendment. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16034, Social Security Act to Reduce Time of Insured Individuals. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16610, Social Security Act to Require Public Health Service Hospitals. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16035, Social Security Act to Eliminate Special Dependency Requirements. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16036, Social Security Act to Provide Benefits for Widowed Fathers. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 9553, Social Security Benefits Increase, 50%. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10637, Social Security Act, Marriage Shall Not Terminate Benefits. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16038, Social Security Act to Eliminate Duration-of- Marriage. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 4228, Social Security, Blind Coverage. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10262, H.R. 4104, Social Security, Chiropractors' Services (2). (Box 78)
      - H.R. 4861, Social Security, Exchange of Credits Between Old Age Survivors and Civil Service. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10256, Social Security, Include Qualified Drugs. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 13933, Social Security Disability Insurance Benefits. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 8238, Social Security, Lump Sum Death Benefit Increase. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 817, Social Security, National Catastrophic Illness Insurance. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10257, Social Security, Optometrists' Services. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10255, Social Security, Outside Income Earnings. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 7855, Social Security, Special Grant Projects Extension. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11818, Social Security, State Expenditure. (Box 78)
      - H.Con.Res. 371, South Vietnam Withdrawal Date. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10847, Soviet Jews Relief Act. (Box 78)
      - H.J.Res. 409, S.E. Asia War Crimes, Congressional Investigation. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 1091, H.R. 4617, State and Local Government Modernization Act. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 737, H.R. 427, Student Congressional Interns (2). (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 905, Supplemental Appropriations to Implement Nixon's Message. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 12863, Supplemental Appropriations. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 875, Suspend Economic and Military Assistance to Thailand, Illegal Drug Traffic. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 5976, Tax Benefits for Unmarried Individuals. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 7839, Tax Deduction for Residential Repair Expenses. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 8645, Tax Exempt Organizations. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 7923, Taxes, Dependent's Exemption. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11862, Tax Reform Act of, 1972. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 4860, Teachers' Sabbatical Leave Act. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 3578, Temporary National Security Commission. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 13147, Terminate Exploitative Activities of Businesses in S. Africa. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11154, Trade and Commerce Restraints. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11809, Transfer of Federal Property to Postal Service. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16849, Treatment of Prisoners in Federal Correctional Institutions, Amended. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11513, H.R. 11515, Two-Dollar Bills. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 971, Underground Nuclear Test Ban Treaty. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 5945, Unemployment Insurance Agricultural Workers. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 12085, U.S.S. Arizona Memorial Visitor Facilities. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 6088, Universal Enrollment Act of, 1971. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 1248, Veterans Housing. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 490, H.Res. 491, U.S.-Vietnam Relationships Study, 1945-67. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 4101, Vietnam Disengagement Act. (Box 78)
      - H.Con.Res. 192, Vietnam Election Congressional Study Team. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 11556, Vietnam Orphans Relief. (Box 78)
      - H.Res. 455, Voice of America Broadcasts in Yiddish. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 12080, Voters Information Act of, 1971. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10862, Voting Rights Act Amendments. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 9029, Wine, Prohibit Imposition of Discriminatory Burdens by the States. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 13116, World's Ocean and Atmosphere Protection Act, 1972. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 10860, Youth Conservation Corps Act Amendments. (Box 78)
      - H.R. 16563, Youth Conservation Corps Program Expanded. (Box 78)
    - Committee and Subject Files
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 79)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 79)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 79)
      - Banking and Currency Committee. (Box 79)
      - Civil Rights. (Box 79)
      - Commerce Committee. (Box 79)
      - District of Columbia Committee. (Box 79)
      - Education and Labor Committee (5). (Box 79)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 79)
      - Health. (Box 79)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 79)
      - Housing. (Box 79)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 79)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee. (Box 79)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 79)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee Poverty. (Box 80*)
      - Public Works Committee. (Box 80*)
      - Revenue Sharing. (Box 80*)
      - Selective Service. (Box 80*)
      - Social Security. (Box 80*)
      - Supersonic Transport. (Box 80*)
      - Transportation. (Box 80*)
      - Veterans Affairs Committee. (Box 80*)
      - Ways and Means Committee. (Box 80*)
      - Welfare. (Box 80*)
      - Legislation, Miscellaneous (3). (Box 80*)
  - 93rd Congress (), 1973-74
    - Bills Sponsored
      - H.R. 4524, Authorization to Impound Funds Approved by Congress. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4382, Brownsville Raid. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 10429, Buy American Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4953, Community Land Grant Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 10865, Community Services Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 14449, Community Services Act of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4522, Compensation for Work Injuries. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 7807, Comprehensive Youth Opportunity Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 8953, Consultive Recognition for Postal Supervisors. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 14094, Development, Volunteer, and Other Community Assistance Programs Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 3641, Economic Opportunity Act of, Extension For 2 Additional Years., 1964 (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 12464, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 15476, H.R. 16459, H.R. 16460, H.R. 16461, H.R. 16462, and H.R. 17182, Equal Opportunity and Full Employment Act of (6)., 1976 (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 3277, Federal Trade Commission Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 11998, Follow Through Program Extension for 1 Year. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 10864, Headstart Programs Extension. (Box 1*)
      - H.Res. 692, Impeachment of Richard M. Nixon (2). (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 15276, Juvenile Delinquency Prevention Act of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 17372, Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention Act Amendments of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 15904, Mexican-American Rural Community Anti-Poverty Act of, 1975. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 8556, Minority Business Assistance Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.J.Res. 709, National Education Policy. (Box 1*)
      - H.J.Res. 897, National Health Week. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 6566, H.R. 6567, Office of Economic Opportunity (2). (Box 1*)
      - H.Con.Res. 174, H.Con.Res. 175, Office of Economic Opportunity (Continuation of Programs) (2). (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4230, H.R. 5706, H.R. 5707, H.R. 6783, and H.R. 7756, Opportunities Industrialization Assistance Act (5). (Box 1*)
      - H.J.Res. 908, Professional Social Work Month. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 3984, H.R. 3986, H.R. 3987, Public Service Employment Act of (1)., 1973 (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 9298, Runaway Youth Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 2334, H.R. 3985, Urban Recreational Opportunity Act of (2)., 1973 (Box 1*)
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.Res. 236, Abolish the Committee on Internal Security. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5592, Abolish the Death Penalty Under All Laws. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 3914, Act for Freedom of Emigration in East-West Trade. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 14486, Additional Funds from HEW for Cause and Treatment of Diabetes. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 7818, Adult Education Amendments of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5401, Agricultural Labor Unemployment Employers Insurance. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5978, Amateur International Athletic Events. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 9527, Amends Maritime Academy Act of, 1958. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 9579, American Folklife Center. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 9706, Armed Services Bill, 60-Day Service After Discharge. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 14598, Arthritis Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation Act of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 11140, Athletic Care Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4714, Authorization to Impound Approved Funds. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5785, Autistic Children Research Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 8349, Bilingual Courts Act. (Box 1*)
      - H.J.Res. 851, Bilingual Education Week. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 6224, Bureaucratic Accountability Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5288, California Desert National Conservation Area. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 5535, Care of the Mentally Retarded in Residential Facilities. (Box 1*)
      - H.Res. 1454, Ceiling Prices on Crude Oil Not Be Increased. (Box 1*)
      - H.J.Res. 580, Census of Agriculture, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 12144, Change Wording on Discharge from Service. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 17290, Chattahoochee River National Area in the State of Georgia. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 15882, Child and Family Services Act of, 1974. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 4228, Child Development Personnel Training Act of, 1973. (Box 1*)
      - H.R. 11986, Civil Rights Act of, Amended., 1964 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13104, Civil Rights Act of, Amended, Military Discharge., 1964 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13199, Civil Rights Act of, Amendment., 1964 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4419, Clean Air Act. (Box 2)
      - H.Con.Res. 189, Collect Overdue Debts. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7774, Colorado River Basin Salinity Control Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7378, Combine the 11th and 12th Naval Districts. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 10602, Community Anticrime Assistance Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 10205, Community Land Grant Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4981, Community School Center Development Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13871, Compensation for Work Injuries Amended. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11931, Comprehensive Campaign Financing Control Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4056, Comprehensive Child Development Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 2302, Comprehensive Older Americans Service Amendments of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13084, Comprehensive School Health Education Act. (Box 2)
      - H.Res. 1136, Condemn Terrorist Killings of School Children in Israel. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4650, Confirmation of OMB Director. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 14539, Congressional Advisory Legislative Line (CALL). (Box 2)
      - H.Res. 244, Congressional Student Interns. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4401, Congressional Oversight Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 2336, Consumer Protection Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 5305, Consumer Credit Protection Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 2413, Consumer Protection Agency Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9168, Consultive Recognition for Postal Supervisors. (Box 2)
      - H.J.Res. 998, Bureau of Labor Statistics, re Consumer Price Index. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 10237, Cost-of-Living Increase in Social Security. (Box 2)
      - H.Res. 1281, Create a Select Committee on Aging. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8327, Credit Against Income Tax for Higher Education. (Box 2)
      - H.Res. 1441, Create a Committee on Intelligence Operations. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 5738, H.R. 1145, Deganawidah-Quetzalcoatl University Grants (2). (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6980, Disability Insurance for Blind Persons. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7854, Elementary and Secondary School Children, Discourage Experimentation on Animals. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6325, D.C. Rent Control Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7265, H.R. 7066, Domestic Volunteer Services Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6260, Economic Opportunity Act of, Amended., 1964 (Box 2)
      - H.Con.Res. 142, Economic Opportunity Act of, 1964. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 528, Educational and Cultural Postal Amendments of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 12618, Education for Exceptional Children Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7892, Educational Services to Handicapped Children. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13480, Ten-year Delimiting Period for Completing Educational Programs. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 525, Education for Handicapped Children Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9096, Elderly and Handicapped Americans Transportation Service Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8268, Elect Coverage of Insurance for Federal Employees. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11151, Election Contributions to Presidential Candidate. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7225, Emergency Extended Unemployment Compensation Program. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 16923, Emergency Jobs Act of, 1974. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 2858, H.R. 10714, Employee Benefit Security Act (2). (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6161, Employment and Inflation Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.J.Res. 568, End Bombing in Cambodia and Laos. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 12378, Energy Information Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11732, Energy Re-Organization Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 12252, Energy Source Legislation. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9111, Equal Credit Opportunity Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8621, Equitable Rents Under the Economic Stabilization Program. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9534, Establishes an Office of U.S. Correctional Ombudsman. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11858, Excise Tax on Certain Cars Using Gasoline. (Box 2)
      - H.Con.Res. 324, Expression of Ideas by Citizens of Soviet Union. (Box 2)
      - H.J.Res. 522, Fair Employment Practices in South African Enterprises. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6021, Family Planning Services and Population Research Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13342, Farm Labor Contractor Registration Act Amendments of, 1974. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8203, Federal Aviation Act of, Amended., 1958 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6316, Federal Disaster Insurance Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 16090, Federal Election Campaign Act of, 1974. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7964, Federally Employed Teachers in Department of Defense Overseas. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9094, Federal Meat Inspection Act, Amended. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8375, Federal Privacy Bill. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7266, H.R. 11119, Federal Protective Service Police Within General Services Administration (2). (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7224, Federal-State Extended Unemployment Compensation Act of, 1970. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8866, Fire Prevention and Control Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 12365, Food Allowance for Older Americans Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6695, Food Stamp Act of, Amended., 1964 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6045, Food Supplement Amendments of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8177, Foreign Assistance Act of, Amended., 1961 (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13989, Foreign Dairy Quality Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 5206, Foreign Trade and Investment Actof, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7884, Forest Conservation and Improvement Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 3460, H.R. 7984, H.R. 7330, Free Flow of Information Act (3). (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11617, Freedom of Access for the Elderly and Handicapped Act for, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 6261, Freedom of Information Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 7902, Gasoline Sales to Independent Gasoline Retailers. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 13912, Grand Jury Reform Act of, 1974. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 3590, Grants to Students Enrolled in Higher Education and Working Part-Time. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 713, Halt Bombing of North Vietnam. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8005, Halt Importation of Rhodesian Chrome. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 15686, Harry S. Truman Memorial Scholarship Act. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 11441, Headstart, Mr. Perkins. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 23, Health Security Act, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 14280, Home Health Care Act of, 1974. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9682, Home Rule for D.C. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 3707, Honest Label Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8028, Improve Workweek of Firefighting Personnel of Executive Agencies. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 15174, Income Taxation for Cooperative Housing Corporations and Condominium Housing. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 9529, Increase Subsistence Payments to State Marine School Students. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8492, Increased Monthly Educational Allowances for Eligible Veterans. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8491, Independent Boards to Review Discharges and Dismissals of Servicemen. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 8090, Independent Oil Marketers Supply Act of, 1973. (Box 2)
      - Internal Revenue Code, Amended
        - H.R. 14546, Alcoholic Beverages. (Box 2)
        - H.R. 15308, Cancellations of Student Loans. (Box 2)
        - H.R. 7094, Retirement Income. (Box 2)
        - H.R. 7095, Medical Expenses Incurred by Persons 65 Years or Older. (Box 2)
      - H.R. 4717, Interstate Commerce in Wine. (Box 2)
      - H.Res. 629, Investigate Grounds for Impeachment of Richard M. Nixon. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 6265, Juvenile Delinquency and Prevention Bill. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17145, Labor-Management and Disclosure Act of, Amended., 1959 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 15228, Land and Water Conservation Fund Act of, Amended., 1965 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 6632, Law Enforcement Officers Bill of Rights. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 6211, H.R. 5109, Legal Services Program, Continuation (2). (Box 3)
      - H.R. 13483, Legislative Reorganization Act of, Amended., 1970 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 16160, H.R. 16465, Limit Prison Medical Research (2). (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17120, Limitations on Inspections of Tax Returns and Disclosures of Information. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 643, Lowering Age Requirements for Membership in the Houses of Congress. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7896, Marine Protection, Research, and Sanctuaries Act of, 1972. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2265, Martin Luther King, Jr. National Holiday. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9364, Mental Retardation Facilities Act, Amended. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 14827, Military Discharge Procedures. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7856, Military Selective Service Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 16951, Monthly Publication of Consumer Price Index for the Elderly. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8058, Motion Picture Films to Pay Prevailing Wages. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7973, Motor Carrier Safety Enforcement Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 11498, Mulholland National Scenic Parkway. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2892, H.R. 1146, National Act for School Construction (2). (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9911, National Blood Bank Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9712, National Catastrophic Disaster Insurance Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9925, National Cemetery in Los Angeles County. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10079, National Child Abuse Prevention Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 11328, National Child Abuse and Neglect Prevention and Treatment Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 14703, National Comprehensive Vision Care Act of, 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9764, National Conservation Area of the California Desert. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 5062, National Crime Victims Compensation Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7441, National Diabetes Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 627, National Grandparents Day. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 15519, National Health Action Corps Act of, 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 13651, National Huntington's Disease Control Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 13272, National Institute of Aging. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4263, National Legal Services Corporation Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4846, National Registration Rights Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 5203, National Science Policy and Priorities Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4932, H.R. 10395, Nation's Beach Resources (2). (Box 3)
      - H.Con.Res. 525, H.Con.Res. 497, Negotiations on the Turkish Opium Ban (2). (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8099, No Aid to North Vietnam. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10541, Noise Control Act of H.Con.Res. 138, Office of Economic Opportunity., 1973 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8897, OEO Appropriations for Fiscal Year Ending, June 30, 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 11105, Older Americans Act, Amended. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17286, Older Americans Home Repair Assistance Act of, 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2251, Older Americans Services Amendments. (Box 3)
      - H.Con.Res. 213, Opposition to Curtailment of Benefits Under Medicare and Medicaid Programs. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 577, Orderly Review of Fee-Paid Oil Import Licenses. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 411, Participate in Presidential Elections for Guam and Virgin Islands. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10589, Peace Act. (Box 3)
      - H.Res. 617, Peace in Middle East. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 3711, Performance Life Disclosure Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4238, Penal Provision of Law Changes. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2009, Pension and Benefits for Veterans Under Social Security. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7865, Percentage of U.S. Oil Imports Be Carried by U.S.-Flagged Vessels. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 138, Popular Election for President and Vice President. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2713, Post-Hospital Home Health Services. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 13182, Postal Reorganization Act Amendments of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8359, Postage-Free Tax Returns. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 11441, Postpone Headstart Fee. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7495, Prescription Drug Freshness Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7494, Prescription Drug Labeling Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7497, Prescription Drug Patent Licensing Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7491, Prescription Drug Price Information Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 5478, Preserve Office of Economic Opportunity. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 6629, Presidential Election Campaign Fund. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 5202, Prisoner Rights Act. (Box 3)
      - H.Res. 878, Prohibition of Extension of Credit by the Export-Import Bank. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17011, Prohibit Certain Conflicts of Interest Regulated by Agencies. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17067, Prohibit Increase in Price of Certain Consumer Commodities. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8490, Prohibit the Inclusion of Certain Information on Discharge Certificates. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 6852, Prohibit Psychosurgery in Federal Health Care Facilities. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 1263, Protection of News Media Sources. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8494, Provide Additional Educational Benefits to Vietnam Era Veterans. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 15364, Provide Hospital and Medical Care to Certain Members of the Armed Services. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17161, Provide Purchasers and Prospective Purchasers of Condominium Housing Credit Without Discrimination. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17278, Public Documents Act of, 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 5739, Public Health Service Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8420, Public Service Employment Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 13075, H.R. 16150, Public Service Employment Act of (2)., 1974 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4822, Public Works and Economic Development Act of, Amended., 1965 (Box 3)